DANA N. GONZALEZ

(240) 205-4585 | danangonzalez@outlook.com

LinkedIn

• LinkedIn Profile

Professional Summary

An experienced professional with 10+ years of organizational team assistance, administrative and office productivity management, and effective internal and external client communications. Independently work to assist in achieving team productivity goals, office efficiency assessment and implementation, and effective guidance and interaction across the leadership hierarchy. Works diligently in a fast paced environment, skilled at multitasking, and driven to assess and implement productivity enhancements where necessary. Excellent proficiency skills in MS Office applications and social media applications. Willing to relocate.

Work History

OASH – OFFICE OF THE ASSISTANT SECRETARY FOR HEALTH (CCHQ) - ROCKVILLE, MD

SEPTEMBER 2023 – FEBRUARY 2024

TRAVEL COORDINATOR

- Plan, process, and coordinate government travel, while ensuring compliance with all applicable
 regulations. Manage travel budgets, in accordance with travel policies and procedures. Maintain
 communications across affected sectors and maintain ongoing updates with executive travelers
 across the country.
- Assemble all of the necessary travel documentation including itineraries, travel authorizations, and passports.
- Review, approve, and manage reimbursements, ensuring that reimbursements are prompt and accurate.
- Manage issuance of travel credit cards, as well as track and reconcile travel expenses.
- Develop lodging and transportation plans, negotiate rates with vendors, research and book travel arrangements.
- Manage travel calendars, and when necessary, coordinate travel with other departments.
- Other administrative tasks include preparing travel reports, manage conference room bookings as necessary, and assist with travel-related projects.

NIH - National Eye Institute (NEI) - BETHESDA, MD Senior Administrative Assistant (Contractor)

JULY 2022 – JUNE 2023 (END OF CONTRACT)

- Assisted in the development, improvement, and evaluation of operational policies and procedures for effectiveness of NEI travel operations.
- Assisted in analyzing program performance; identify issues and develop recommendations for improvement; drafted standard operating procedures and guidelines.
- Managed NEI's Conference Approval Program.
- Coordinate with staff to implement improvements; develop database modules and plan additional features for the management of program-related travel data.
- Maintain and update internal websites, databases and travel systems; coordinate internal site improvements.
- Reviewed and tracked incoming correspondence and action items; follow up with appropriate staff to ensure completion within deadlines.

• Insured all NEI travel planners and administrative staff are apprised of current travel procedures for conference requests and conference approvals.

COMMERCIAL PROPERTY MANAGEMENT

May 2016 to July 2022

Brandywine Realty Trust – Vienna, VA **Property Administrator**

- Maintained direct contact with tenants and operations personnel to maintain positive relationships, ensured appropriate problem solving solutions, and exceed tenant expectations.
- Developed and maintained business relationships with vendors.
- Tracked accounts receivables, collaborated on budget reporting, and processed invoices.

Bridge Commercial Real Estate – Silver Spring, MD **Assistant Property Manager**

- Monitored progress of construction and maintenance projects and notify appropriate individuals of project updates, delays and schedule changes.
- Analyzed, interpreted, and provided appropriate explanation of tenant leases.
- Managed the generation, processing, and payment of invoices.
- Generated pre-posting reports.
- Collaborated with building owners to strategize on improvements to tenant outreach programs.
- Expertly resolved commercial tenant conflicts.
- custom

Special Assistant to the Director – Rockville, MD Department of Health and Human Services

June 2015 to Sept 2015

- Delivered top-notch administrative support to office staff, promoting excellence in office operations.
- Implemented SharePoint to streamline office communication and efficiency in productivity
- Performed general office duties in a fast paced environment, greeted and welcomed visitors, managed multi-line phone system to route calls and deliver staff messages.
- Communicated expeditiously with supervisors, fully explained issues and participated on the team to strategize on appropriate solutions.
- Created and updated physical records and digital files to maintain current, accurate and compliant documentation.
- Developed non-standard correspondence to meet organizational needs and enhance communication with stakeholders.

Guest Relations Associate /Team Leader – Silver Spring, MD American Film Institute

January 2011 to June 2015

- Provided dynamic service skills to ensure expert service to patrons.
- Managed transportation arrangements, accommodations, and venue schedules for filmographers.
- Maintained files and travel records that boosted efficiency and file organization.
- Maintained program operating accounts in balance and ran daily reports to verify totals.
- Improved existing database and ensured its accuracy.

Skills

- Project Management Assistance
- Expert in MS Office Suite Applications
- Assessment of Process Proficiency
- Internal and External Communication
- Information File Tracking

- Process Optimization Development
- Spreadsheet Development
- Database Research and Maintenance
- Technical Process Troubleshooting

Education

Bachelor of Arts: History Alvernia University, Reading, PA